Contact

Israel +972584830390 (Mobile) adler.vitalii@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/vitalii-adler (LinkedIn) adlerv.com (Personal)

Top Skills

Java

Core Java

Hibernate

Languages

Hebrew

English

Russian

Certifications

Express JS

Building Modern Projects with React

React-Redux Professional Development

Vitalii Adler

Software Engineer at Meadow

Tel Aviv

Summary

Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with a wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Able to handle any part of the process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 3 years of related experience.

Experience

Meadow

Software Engineer September 2020 - Present (2 months)

Tel Aviv, Israel

Optisor LTD

Full Stack Developer

July 2018 - September 2020 (2 years 3 months)

Haifa Area, Israel

Participated in design and development front-end side.

Outlined high-volume, high-scale web front ends for assets requiring responsive designs.

Worked in Agile-driven environment to effectively maintain project timelines and utilize available resources.

Designed and updated layouts to meet usability and performance requirements.

Tools (React/Redux, JavaScript, CSS3/HTML5, Bootstrap)

Also participated in development backend side:

Designed and developed Java/J2EE/JS applications.

Used most popular frameworks and design patterns.

Developed controllers, services logic and data structure for storing in DB on Server side.

Tools (Swagger, Java, Spring Security, Spring Data, Spring Cloud, MongoDB)

Megapolis Invest LTD Information Technology Specialist 2016 - December 2018 (2 years)

- Remote technical support for company customers
- Setting up computers and office equipment
- Troubleshooting and support Office 2016
- Troubleshooting and support operating systems (MacOS, Windows OS)
- Manual Software Testing
- Support company server and network
- Writing Support Documentation

Baltic-Tour-Service LTD IT specialist 2012 - 2016 (4 years)

Setting up computers, testing, detection and troubleshooting of computers and copying equipment. Installation and configuration of programs and software.

Assistance in the selection of software required to meet the needs of the company.

Education

Tel-Ran, Educational Center Graduated, Full Stack Developer · (2018 - 2019)

High School of Computer science Graduate · (1994 - 1999)